hey everybody welcome to this a1 english
listening practice video you can use
this video to practice your listening
and comprehension as i speak before we
start remember to download the listening
time podcast and become a member at
patreon.com
listeningtime to receive my specialized
training which will help you understand
native speakers and if you want my
advanced podcast then become a listening
time family member okay today we're
gonna talk about some more countries
last time i told you about my experience
in mexico france portugal and spain
today i want to tell you about a few
other countries that i've been to
let me start with italy i spent two
weeks in italy in 2019
this was probably my favorite trip i had
the opportunity to go to many cities and
towns in this country i started my trip
in bologna which was a great experience
i had some really delicious food in this
city and it was my first time eating at
a real italian restaurant i'll never
forget it i had a few different local
dishes which were incredible also i ate
the best ice cream ever when i was in
this city
next i went to florence which was one of
the most beautiful cities i've ever seen
i'm sure that some of you agree with me
then we rented a car and drove through
tuscany this was an awesome road trip we
drove through beautiful hills fields and
vineyards
this was my favorite region of italy
it's so unique there there's no other
place like it lastly we went to rome and
enjoyed the amazing history there of
course we loved going to the coliseum
and seeing the ancient buildings there
okay now let me talk a little bit about
peru i went to peru with a friend in
2018 to see machu picchu
everyone wants to see machu picchu right
so we stayed in the city of cusco and
took some different tours of the area we
saw some interesting ruins around cusco
and we really enjoyed the beautiful
nature there and the city of cusco is
also a cool place to explore
but of course the best part of the trip
was seeing machu picchu this ancient
city is hidden in the mountains and it's
not easy to get there
we had to take two buses and a train to
arrive there but it was worth it the
view of machu picchu from above was
incredible we sat for a long time just
looking at the city i couldn't believe
that i was there we didn't take a tour
but there were many tours when we were
there so we heard some tour guides
talking about the history of machu
picchu then we walked around the city
and explored the different parts this
experience was completely unique and
i'll never forget it okay lastly i'm
just gonna say a few things about the uk
specifically london i only stayed in
london for one day before i flew to
italy so i saw very little but i walked
a lot during that short time and i loved
the city the weather was nice when i was
there so i watched the sunset from the
river i also went to my first christmas
market there
so even though i was only there for one
day i really liked it i was sad that i
couldn't stay longer maybe in the future
i'll be able to go back
so now you know the different countries
that i've traveled to
leave a comment and tell me if you've
traveled to any of these countries
before you go remember to download the
listening time podcast and become a
member at patreon.com
listeningtime to receive my specialized
training which will help you understand
native speakers and if you want my
advanced podcast then become a listening
time family member also subscribe to the
channel click on the bell and follow us
on instagram i'll see you next time
you